…确定这是什么的问题
...a matter of establishing what this is.
如果这确实是恐怖主义行为 那么是谁造成的
If indeed this was an act of terrorism, then who caused it?
整个东海岸的所有电力都用光了
All of the electricity across the entire Eastern Seaboard is out.
人们命令呆在室内直到接到进一步的通知并且…
People ordered to stay indoors until further notice and to...
…简直就是天启
...is nothing short of apocalyptic.
…大都会区 除了芝加哥
...metropolitan areas, in addition to Chicago,
被完全包围
are completely surrounded.
我们仍在等待官方公告
We're still awaiting an official announcement,
但是国会被认为是无条件接受的
but Congress is believed to have accepted unconditionally
所有停战条款
all terms of armistice offered.
…在过去的几个小时里恢复了电源
...and with power restored in the last few hours,
-戒严…-这太花时间了
-martial law... -This is taking too long.
现在所有的美国军队都回到了他们的基地
Now all US military forces are returning to their bases
带着命令转身退后直到下一个命令…
with orders to turn in arms and stand down until further orders...
报告现在从东京 雅加达 罗马传播开来
Reports are spreading now from Tokyo, Jakarta, Rome.
与外部新闻来源的联系是零星的
Contact with outside news sources has been sporadic
由于特伦顿电网的毁灭性故障
since the devastating failure of the Trenton power grid,
但目击者证实…
but eyewitnesses confirm...
…大多数国际政府似乎都遵守…
...that the majority of international governments appear to comply...
警官 我要往北上去
Officer, I need to get up north.
你要去哪里 警探
Where you going, Detective?
你没有接到命令
You not get orders?
停车 停车
Stop the car. Stop the car.
把手从方向盘上拿开
Take your hands off the wheel.
-停止发动机 -嗯…
-Stop the engine. -Um...
-哦 我的…停车
-Oh, my... -Stop the car!
…似乎追随了美国的领导
...appear to have followed the US' lead
并且正在与第一批立法者力量进行谈判
and are entering into negotiations with this first wave of Legislator forces.
听着 我们应该给学校打电话吗 可能有个计划
Look, should we call the school? There may be a plan.
我不会翻身的 我们需要出去重新组合 然后反击
I'm not rolling over! We need to get out and regroup, then fight back.
J.
J... John!
John.
转身
Turn around.
Turn around!
快点 约翰
Come on, John.
关闭非常有序
The shutdown was very orderly.
有某种程度的合作
There's been a sort of a level of cooperation
你可以在这里看到
that you can see here.
我爱你 鲁拉
I love you, Rula.
另一个避免湖滨驾车的提醒
Another reminder to avoid Lake Shore Drive
如果你不是今晚被邀请参加团结庆典的幸运千人之一
if you're not one of the lucky thousands invited to tonight's unity celebration.
这项活动已经进行了一年多
This event has been in the works for the better part of a year,
市长李艾德将出席
with Mayor Ed Lee expected to attend.
所有的标志都指向这个…
All signs are pointing to this...
你见过太阳落在湖的另一边吗
You ever see the sun set on the other side of the lake?
不 太阳从这边落下 笨蛋 西侧
No. The sun sets this side, dummy. West side.
是啊
Yeah.
我知道
I know.
我晚点来看你 好吗
I'll come and see you later, all right?
嘿 哟
Hey, yo.
船准备好了 伙计
Boat's all ready, man,
所以你今天把它拿下来 我们就离开这里
so you pull this off today, we're out of here.
嘿 冷静点
Hey, cool it.
全天候盯着我看
Got eyes on me 24-7.
不 去那边看看她
No shit. Check her out, up there.
哟 每天 那个女巫都像钟表一样看着我
Yo, every day, that witch be watching me like clockwork.
嘿 我看见一只老鼠
Hey, I see a rat.
纳克
Narc!
哦
Oh...
走吧
Let's go.
-你兄弟是个传奇 伙计 哟 快点
-Your bro's a legend, man. -Yo, come on.
你最后一次见到它是什么时候
When's the last time you seen one?
蟑螂
A roach?
很久以前 来吧 伙计 我们走 听着 我今天不能迟到
A long time ago. Come on, man, let's go. Look, I can't be late today.
我应该像你哥哥那样闯进来 把整堆蚂蚁都铲平
I should break in like your brother did and bulldoze that whole ant heap.
他们不能永远躲在那里 伙计
They can't hide down there forever, man.
我马上就好
I'll be ready in a minute.
我时间不多
I don't have much time.
但我想见你
But I wanted to see you.
好吧 那我们最好把生意让开
Well, then we'd better get business out of the way.
我不能这么做
I can't do this.
我们去睡觉吧
Let's go to bed.
我们在做什么 这是个错误
What are we doing? This is a mistake.
没有错误 只有命运
There's no such thing as a mistake. There's only fate.
你是警察 你不会被抓住的 -对不起
-You're a cop. You won't get caught. -I'm sorry.
等待 等待
Wait. Wait.
你忘了你来这里是为了什么
You forgot what you came here for.
提防带礼物的希腊人
Beware Greeks bearing gifts.
-我有一个二手身份证-老鹰降落了
-I got a secondhand ID. -So the Eagle has landed?
凤凰 你应该注意
Phoenix. You should pay attention.
你看到了吗 二手货是二手货
You got a visual? Secondhand is secondhand.
你还从下面得到授权吗
You still got authorization from below?
他们在计划一件大事
They're planning something big.
它们不存在
They don't exist.
我们就是这么说外星人的
That's what we said about aliens.
真有趣
That's funny.
还记得柳条公园吗
Remember Wicker Park?
是的 蟑螂把它们弄成了尘土 他们走了
Yeah, the roaches fucked them into dust. They're gone.
不要用那个词
Don't use that word.
什么
What?
这是什么时候开始成为你的个人工作空间的
Since when has this become your personal work space?
在柳条公园之后 抵抗运动没有被消灭
The resistance wasn't wiped out after Wicker Park.
他们走到地上 我明白了
They went to ground. I figured it out.
他们通过分类广告进行交流
They're communicating through the classifieds.
他们的网络在皮尔森重组 就在我们眼皮底下
Their network regrouped here in Pilsen, right under our noses.
你什么都没有
You got nothing that shows that.
论文…这些是纪念物
Theses... These are memorials.
立法者把他们都抓起来了 你在找鬼 比尔
Legislators got 'em all. You're searching for ghosts, Bill.
如果我们现在不采取行动 我们将面临全面的叛乱
If we don't act now, we're facing a full-blown insurgency.
我建议你自己保留这个想法
I suggest you keep that idea to yourself.
好吧 太晚了 已经踢到楼下了
Well, too late. Already kicked it downstairs.
在专员的办公桌上
It's on the commissioner's desk.
你为什么这么做
Why did you do that?
他们没有走
They're not gone.
-你没被跟踪 -没有
-You weren't followed? -No.
训练结束了
Training's over.
你支持这个
And you back this?
我支持第一
I back Number One.
通往封闭区的路是穿过士兵阵地
The way to the Closed Zone is through Soldier Field.
队伍今晚出发
Team goes tonight.
这是士兵场
It's Soldier Field.
团结集会
The Unity Rally?
从巴博萨得到你需要的
Get what you need from Barbosa.
士兵场离封闭区有几英里
Soldier Field is miles from the Closed Zone.
-那是怎么让我们回到里面的 -我相信你
-How's that get us back inside? -I'm trusting you.
-他会送货的 他必须这么做 今天就是
-He'll deliver. -He has to. Today's the day.
加布里埃尔・德拉蒙德 上午7:04
Gabriel Drummond, 7:04 a.m.
哦 好了 就这样……
Oh, there it goes. There it goes...
哦 结束了 这是尖叫声
Oh, it's over. It's a squeaker.
那是一分半钟的事
That was a matter of a minute and a half.
四处走走 从其他角度看一看
Walk around, take a look from other angles.
哦
Oh!
15分钟
Fifteen minutes.
另一个避免湖滨驾车的提醒
Another reminder to avoid Lake Shore Drive
如果你不是今晚被邀请参加团结庆典的幸运千人之一
if you're not one of the lucky thousands invited to tonight's unity celebration.
这项活动已经进行了一年多
This event has been in the works for the better part of a year,
市长李艾德将出席
with Mayor Ed Lee expected to attend.
所有迹象都表明这是一个罕见的场合
All signs are pointing to this being one of those rare occasions
当立法者可能只是露面的时候
when the Legislators might just make an appearance.
车辆正在士兵场周围绕行
Traffic's being routed around Soldier Field,
人们很早就出现了
and folks are showing up early.
这是多么美好的夜晚啊
What a night here this is.
值得庆祝的事 另一个提醒…
Lots to celebrate. Another reminder...
你明白吗
You got it or what?
…如果你不是幸运的几千人之一
...if you're not one of the lucky thousands
应邀参加今晚的团结庆典
invited to tonight's unity celebration.
这项活动已经进行了一年多
This event has been in the works for the better part of a year,
市长李艾德将出席
with Mayor Ed Lee expected to attend.
所有迹象都表明这是一个罕见的场合
All signs are pointing to this being one of those rare occasions
当立法者可能只是露面的时候
when the Legislators might just make an appearance.
车辆正在士兵场周围绕行
Traffic's being routed around Soldier Field,
人们很早就出现了
and folks are showing up early.
这是多么美好的夜晚啊 值得庆祝的事
What a night here this is. Lots to celebrate.
在这里
Here.
另一个避免湖滨驾车的提醒
Another reminder to avoid Lake Shore Drive
如果你不是幸运的千人之一…
if you're not one of the lucky thousands...
希望你能好好利用它
Hope you put it to good use.
这项活动在一年中的大部分时间都在进行中
This event has been in the works for the better part of a year.
所有迹象都表明这是一个罕见的场合
All signs are pointing to this being one of those rare occasions
当立法者可能只是露面的时候
when the Legislators might just make an appearance.
拜托
Please.
我什么都没做
I haven't done anything.
-我什么都没做 -嘿 嘿 别管她
-I haven't done anything. -Hey. Hey, leave her alone.
拜托 我们能不能…
Please, can we just...
行星外运输…
Off-planet transport...
嘿 快点 兄弟 你得看看这个
Hey, hurry up, bro. You got to check this out.
她只需要汽油
All she needs is gas.
-该死的 哟 -对吗
-Damn, yo. -Right?
她也很快
She's fast, too.
一定要从外面过去
Got to be to get past what's out there,
但是没有检查站 所以我们到了另一边
but there's no checkpoint, so we get to the other side,
这就是自由 宝贝
and it's freedom, baby.
希望如此
Let's hope so.
那么 你拿到烟了吗
So, did you get the cigarette?
-我当然明白了 -妈的 那我们就离开这里
-Of course I got it. -Shit, then we're out of here.
哟 我就要像披头巾高手一样来对付这些蟑螂了
Yo, I'm about to come like Scarf ace on these roaches.
呸
Bah!
我不打不倒
I'm not going down without a fight.
哟 你用什么换来的
Yo, what did you trade for that?
直接现金 而且已经满了
Straight cash, and it's fully loaded.
哦 我们需要的汽油钱
Oh, the cash we need for gas?
冷静 伙计 这是一项投资
Chill, man. It's an investment.
你为什么总是绊倒我 伙计
Why are you always trippin', man?
人们都在为我们在这里得到的东西而渴望
People are jonesing for what we got out here!
什么 你觉得你现在在大联盟 尤吉斯 哈
What, you think you in the big leagues now, Jurgis, huh?
哟 那该死的东西会给我们带来严重的麻烦
Yo, that shit right there will get us in some serious trouble.
我讨厌这种口对口的推销
I'm sick of this hand-to-mouth hustling.
你认为我不是
You think I'm not?
-我得走了 伙计 去
-I got to go, man. -Go?
-我们是搭档 伙计 任何…合作伙伴
-We're partners, man. Any... -Partners?
伙计 我承担风险
Man, I take the risk.
我今天看到有人被带走了
I saw someone get taken today.
是的 好吧 我在外面忙着 结束交易
Yeah, well, I'm out here hustling, closing the deals,
当你在婴儿床上的时候 只是在踢背 冷 嗯
while you're at the crib just kicking back, chilling, huh?
听着 我得照顾好自己和鲁拉
Look, I got to take care of myself and Rula.
你和Rula
You and Rula?
好吧 伙计 很好
All right, man, fine.
准备好你的侧片 我要单独去
Have your side piece. I'll go solo.
我不是在和你玩 尤吉斯
I'm not playing with you, Jurgis.
嘿 快点 寒冷 寒冷 哟 我不是…
-Hey, come on. Chill, chill. -Yo, I'm not...
嘿 嘿 嘿 冷静 哟
Hey. hey, hey, chill, yo.
倒霉
Shit!
上车
Get in the car.
特别部门没什么好做的
Special Branch ain't got nothing better to do?
来自当地
From your local.
你想要什么
What do you want?
你对凤凰城了解多少
What do you know about Phoenix?
我不是你的毒品
I'm not one of your narcs.
你在这里干什么 加布里埃尔
What are you doing down here, Gabriel?
你很幸运有你的工作
You're lucky to have your job.
我没有问你
I didn't ask you for it.
我不希望你像你哥哥那样结束
I don't want you winding up like your brother.
-你是说死了 -我是说站错了方向
-You mean dead? -I mean on the wrong side.
它在家庭中运行
It runs in the family.
你无权谈论我的家人
You have no right to be talking about my family.
你爸爸是我的搭档
Your dad was my partner.
我对此负有责任
I have a responsibility to that.
你有自己的选择
You have a choice to make yourself.
别弄错了
Don't make the wrong one.
离开这里
Get out of here.
你有我的钱吗
You got my money?
嘿 我们开始吧 我拿到烟了
Hey, let's do this. I got the cigarette.
嘿 嘿 嘿 你说把它拿过来
Hey, hey, hey. You said to bring it here.
当选
Get in.
嘿 我只是想得到报酬 伙计
Yo, I'm just trying to get paid, man.
-不 我不进去 不-来吧
-No, I'm not getting in, no. -Come on.
嘿 嘿 嘿
Hey, hey, hey.
嘿 哟 看 伙计
Hey, yo, look, man.
伙计 你来找我了 记得吗
Man, you came to me, remember?
-把这个放在 -哟 这是什么
-Put this on. -Yo, what is this?
哟 这是什么
Yo, what is this?
等待 等等 等等 等等 等等 等等
Wait. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
哟 没有人说什么也不去
Yo. No one said nothing about going nowhere.
走出
Get out.
跟着我
Follow me.
走吧
Let's go.
柳条公园
Wicker Park.
我们在这里做什么
What are we doing here?
你想得到报酬 是吗
You want to get paid, don't you?
那件夹克对你来说还是太大了
That jacket's still too big for you.
小弟弟
Baby brother.
怎么搞的
What happened?
我们还没来得及弄到蟑螂 他们就把我们弄到手了
Before we could get the roaches, they got us.
我是唯一一个成功的人
I'm the only one that made it out.
等等 你的…
Wait, your...
你的错误…
Your bug...
-在哪里 -走了
-Where's it at? -Gone.
-不 那是不可能的 -我们中的一些人现在脱离了网络
-No, that's impossible. -A few of us are off the grid now.
-谁很少 -我不认识其他人
-Few of who? -I don't know the others.
其他人不认识我 这样更好
The others don't know me. It's better that way.
我不再存在了
I don't exist anymore.
在某些方面 我已经死了
In some ways, I am dead.
你找不到我
You couldn't come find me?
我想去 但到处都是毒品 你知道的 即使在Pilsen
I wanted to, but there's narcs everywhere. You know that. Even in Pilsen.
德拉蒙德兄弟回来了
The Drummond brothers are back.
永远好 我接通了 雷夫
For good. I'm dialed in, Rafe.
我的朋友 他住在湖边 他有这艘船
My friend, he lives by the lakeshore. He has this boat.
-我们有这个计划…
-We have this plan and... -G.
-…我们要穿过湖…
-...we're gonna go across the lake... -G.
这个…就是这个计划
This... is the plan.
我知道你会明白的
I knew you'd get it.
那么 我给你买了什么
So, what'd I get you?
信息
Information.
谁的信息
Information for who?
只有头号人才知道
Only Number One knows.
一号
-Number One? -Mm-hmm.
那到底是谁
Who the hell is that?
没有人知道 就像我告诉你的
No one knows. It's like I told you.
这样更好
It's better that way.
糟糕的时刻即将来临
Bad times coming.
在这里 这将帮助你摆脱困境
Here. This will help you get out.
去湖边小屋
Go to the lake house.
不是下周 不是明天 现在
Not next week, not tomorrow. Now.
-在天黑之前 -跟我来
-Before it get dark. -Come with me.
又不是了 雷夫 不要再这样
Not again, Rafe. Not again!
我们得照顾好自己
We just got to take care of ourselves.
我们想出去的那天爸爸怎么说
What'd Dad say the day we tried to get out?
重新组合 反击
Regroup. Fight back.
-他现在死了 -注意你的嘴
-And he dead now. -Watch your mouth.
让蟑螂来拿走他们想要的东西 如果他们这么想的话
Let the roaches come and take what they want if they want it so bad.
我们可以从头再来 雷夫
And we can start all over, Rafe.
我们可以回到过去的样子
We can get back to the way that things used to be.
你不明白吗
Don't you get it?
和谐 和平 团结……全是胡说八道
Harmony, peace, unity... it's all bullshit.
这是个谎言 加布 他们会拿走一切
It's a lie, Gabe. They gonna take everything.
再过几年 他们就会把我们剥得一文不值
In a few years, they'll have stripped us to nothing.
再给我一次机会点燃足够大的火 让全世界都能看到
Got one more chance to light a fire big enough so the whole world can see.
向在场的所有人证明蟑螂是可以被打败的
To prove to everybody out there that the roaches can be beat.
点燃火柴
Light a match.
点燃一场战争
Ignite a war.
只要我们反击 我们就有机会
Long as we fight back, we got a chance.
为什么你总是要成为英雄
Why you always got to be the hero?
你得选一边
You got to pick a side.
加布 你得选一边 总有一天 你必须 否则就是这样
You got to pick a side, Gabe. One day, you have to, or this is it.
你得走了
You got to go.
盖布 当这一切结束的时候
Gabe, when this is all over,
我会找到你的
I'll find you.
我保证
I promise.
你得走了
You just got to go.
现在
Now.
抓住他了
Got him.
宝贝 怎么了
Baby, what's going on?
我们要出去了
We're getting out.
可以
Okay.
好吧 在我们这么做之前 我们为什么不…
Well, before we do that, why don't we just...
抓住这个 只带你能带的东西
Grab this. And take only what you can carry.
你做了什么
What did you do?
会有麻烦的
There's gonna be some trouble.
加布里埃尔 这是什么意思
Gabriel, what is that supposed to mean?
什么 拜托 你把我吓坏了
What, come on, you're freaking me out.
Rafe…
Rafe...
是活着的
is alive.
你哥哥
Your brother?
是啊
Yeah.
很好 加布里埃尔
Nice try, Gabriel.
他说了什么 你在哪里见到他的
What did he say? Where did you see him?
这就足够我们维持几个星期了
That's about enough to last us a couple weeks.
在那之后 我们必须自己去做
After that, we're gonna have to make it on our own.
不 我们不能通过第一个检查站
No, we won't make it past the first checkpoint.
如果我们过湖就不行了
Not if we go across the lake.
我有一条船可以用
I've got a boat that we can use.
那边什么都没有 包括法律 很危险
There's nothing over there. There's no law. It's dangerous.
你没听我说
You're not listening to me.
他们在计划什么
They're planning something.
好吧 如果我们走了 我们就参与进来了 没办法
Okay, and if we go, we are involved. No way.
-宝贝 宝贝 来吧 -没有
-Baby, baby. Come on. -No.
加布里埃尔 如果你想保护我的安全 你需要留下来
Gabriel, if you want to keep me safe, you need to stay.
拜托
Please.
-不 我不能-不 加布里埃尔
-No, I can't. -No, Gabriel.
-我不能 我不能-加布里埃尔 这太疯狂了
-I can't, I can't. -Gabriel, this is crazy.
拜托 我们谈谈这个
Please, let's talk about this!
键入此 发送到PDHQ 快
Type this. Send it to PDHQ. Fast.
移动
Move!
-他们能追踪我们吗 -不 我有一些镜像IP
-Can they track us? -No. I got a few mirror IPs.
抓住他了 这是你的目标
Got him. There's your target.
把你自己当作特别的分支机构
Consider yourself as informed as Special Branch.
那么 他是谁
So, who is he?
只是另一个合作者 市长的副手
Just another collaborator. Mayor's deputy.
不 不
No, no.
他是谁
Who is he?
他带着炸弹
He carries the bomb.
分类广告 -还有空间再放一个吗
-Classifieds. -Got room for one more?
再一个
One more.
最新版本
The late edition?
他们把划痕校对到3:30
They proofread the scratch till 3:30.
真的很重要 丽顿豪斯
Real important, Rittenhouse.
是啊 谢谢您
Yeah. Thank you.
这是一个请求
This is a request going out.
你好
Hi.
谁想先去
Who wants to go first?
把他从桌子上拿下来
Get him off the table.
下一步 快点
Next. Hurry.
把她带进来
Get her in here.
他的心率低于极限 使他的虫子很难受
His heart rate went below the limit and distressed his bug.
无人机是所有昆虫的母体 我们现在得把你的拿出来
Drones are maternal to all bugs. We have to get yours out now.
知道了
Got it.
别动 我给你缝针
Don't move. I'll stitch you up.
好的
All right.
这三个虫子是三个内部人 心脏病发作 癌症 不幸的车祸
These three bugs are the three insiders. Heart attack, cancer, unlucky car wreck.
市中心的人们 一尘不染的记录
Downtown folks, spotless records.
另外三个对你的司机来说足够好了
The other three are good enough for your drivers.
我现在需要两个
I need two now.
好吧 我的班明天早上7点结束
All right, my shift ends at 7:00 a.m. tomorrow.
这是最新的我可以将他们作为死者登录的
That's the latest I can log them in as deceased.
只要他们能胜任就行 在那之后他们会得到身份证 他们就是
That's as long as they're good for. They get ID'd after that, they're it.
你需要这些盘子把虫子放在嘴里
You're gonna need these plates to keep the bugs down in their mouth.
Semper FI 中士
Semper fi, Sergeant.
我一直相信死后的生活
I always did believe in life after death.
是你吗 爸爸
Is that you, Father?
回来吧
Come on back.
你抓了我什么
What you got me?
最后一个
The last of it.
在这儿等着
Wait here.
现在 我想我不必告诉你他们会怎么做
Now, I assume I don't have to tell you what they'll do
如果他们在你的人身上发现这个
if they find this on your person.
你从哪儿弄来的
Where'd you get this?
他们的船也坠毁了
Their ship crashed, too.
最好与天然纤维 人发 棉花或羊毛搭配
Attaches best to natural fiber, human hair, cotton or wool,
但因为它不是化学成分 所以扫描仪无法检测到
but because it's not chemically based, it's undetectable to scanners.
因为它是有机的 它通过所有的安全
Because it's organic, it passes through all security.
你可以把这个偷运到任何地方
You can smuggle this in anywhere.
当你武装它的时候 它是变色龙
And when you arm it, it's a chameleon.
我们如何武装它
How do we arm it?
双击会给你60秒
Double tap gives you about 60 seconds.
司机在楼下
Drivers are downstairs.
神圣地狱
Holy hell.
把它拿下来
Take that off.
你还不如穿上靶子
You may as well be wearing a target.
好吧 这些植入物明天早上7点被记录为死亡
All right, these implants get logged as deceased at 7:00 a.m. tomorrow.
在那之后 你就死定了
After that, you're dead to the world.
你知道如果皮尔森能正确识别我们的身份 他们会怎么样
You know what happens to Pilsen if they correctly ID us.
与任何朋友或家人在之前和之后的任何接触
Any contact, before and after, with any friends or family
使整个行动处于危险之中
puts the entire operation at risk.
记得
Remember...
他让我们找到他们
he gets us to them.
没有人被活捉
No one gets taken alive.
可以
Okay.
准备好了吗 我们走吧
You ready? Here we go.
勇气
Courage.
-从这里右转 -我明白了
-Make a right out of here. -I got it.
芝加哥人…
People of Chicago...
欢迎来到特别的聚会之夜
welcome to a special night of coming together,
分享
of sharing.
今晚 我们有一些非常特别的客人加入我们
And tonight, we have some very special guests joining us.
在第一次接触之前 我们的政治制度被打破了
Before first contact, our political system was broken.
我们在国会大厅里自相残杀
We were fighting among ourselves in the halls of Congress
在这座大城市的街道上
and on the streets of this great city,
慢慢流血至死
slowly bleeding to death.
我们需要改变
And we needed change.
我们需要有人给我们一个更好的方法
We needed someone to show us a better way.
好吧 事实本身就说明了问题
Well, the facts speak for themselves.
自然资源产量增加了十倍
Natural resource production has increased tenfold.
就业率达到创纪录水平 犯罪率创历史新低
Employment is at record levels. Crime at an all-time low.
玩这个游戏是值得的
Pays to play the game.
我们要感谢立法者
And we have the Legislators to thank
为了美国的复兴
for this American renaissance!
所以 你能和我一起给他们一个真正的家乡的欢迎吗
So, will you please join me in giving them a real hometown welcome
这真的表达了我们的谢意
that truly shows our appreciation
九年的和平与繁荣
for nine years of peace and prosperity!
玛丽约翰逊 晚上8:39
Mary Johnson, 8:39 p.m.
车窗朝下 先生
Window down, sir.
先生 请欣赏今晚的演出
Enjoy the show tonight, sir.
人群继续欢呼
[crowd continues cheering
我在里面
I'm inside.
E 部分
"E" section.
女士们先生们 美利坚合众国
Ladies and gentlemen, the United State of America.
女士们先生们 表演得真好
What a performance, ladies and gentlemen.
九年前的多彩重现
A colorful reenactment of nine years ago.
他们像钟表一样运转着 我们得把它给他们
They're running this thing like clockwork. We got to give it to 'em.
他现在要离开贵宾区
He's leaving the VIP section now.
这是多么的荣幸…
What a privilege it is...
你能看见他吗
Can you see him?
我看见他了 他在球场上 我们就位了
I see him. He's on the field. We're in position.
他不会来的
He's not coming to
他走另一条路 朝你身后的隧道走去
He's going the other way, towards the tunnel behind you.
知道了
Got it.
女士们先生们 请起立迎接我们的立法机关
Ladies and gentlemen, please rise to greet our Legislature.
他马上就来找你
He's coming right at you.
罗伯特・沃茨
Robert Watts?
是本 本・西蒙 德雷克塞尔驱动器
It's Ben. Ben Simon. Drexel Drive.
保持移动
Keep it moving.
对不起 很抱歉
Sorry about it. Sorry about it.
放开我
Hands off of me.
请给我时间翻译
Allow me time to translate.
在句子之间呼吸
Breathe between sentences.
我们需要让他们先沟通
We need to allow them to communicate first.
…这是全城的零-4派遣 浓烟
...this is Zero-4 citywide dispatch. Heavy smoke.
我们有一半在区域安全部门…
We got half in zone security unit...
…不明原因 可能的立法者
...unaccounted for, possible Legislator.
来吧
Come on.
别动
Don't move!
上车 当选
Get in the car! Get in!
把它们放在外面
Keep them out there!
把人群往后退 特此命令…
Keep that crowd back! You are hereby ordered...
加油 我们得走了
Come on! We got to go!
哦 不
Oh, no.
哦 他妈的
Oh, fuck.
你和我一起去
You and me go together.
我们一直到早上7点
We got till 7:00 a.m.
人们需要理解的是 这是一场战争
What people need to understand is this is a war.
在秩序和混乱之间
Between order and chaos.
在民主和无政府状态之间
Between democracy and anarchy.
伊戈专员 叛乱正在重组吗
Commissioner Igoe, is the insurgency reorganizing?
叛乱  自从威克公园以来 没有人提到过这个词
"Insurgency." No one's mentioned that word since Wicker Park.
有传言说猎人被带进来了
There are rumors that hunters are being brought in.
正在采取措施 但为了保持有效性
Measures are being taken, but to preserve their effectiveness,
我不想讨论他们
I'm not gonna discuss them.
随着形势的发展 我们会不断更新您的信息
And we will keep you updated as the situation evolves.
-不 这里有个问题 谢谢
-No, a question over here. -Thank you.
指挥官 伊戈专员准备好了
Commander. Commissioner Igoe is ready for you.
这次他们从地球外引进了猎人
They're bringing in hunters this time from off planet.
-他们不能那样做 -我们有一个身份证
-They can't do that. -The one ID we have,
圣安东尼的前牧师指向皮尔森
the ex-priest from Saint Anthony's, points to Pilsen.
你知道那意味着什么
You know what that means.
我们可以自己清理
We can clean this up ourselves.
是的 没人在说清理
Yeah, nobody's talking about a cleanup.
皮尔森不是威克公园 局长
Pilsen isn't Wicker Park, Commissioner.
是的 还没有
Yeah, not yet.
他们在这附近放火
They torch this neighborhood,
网络会像上次一样接地
the network will go to ground just like they did last time.
你知道吗 比尔 你太多愁善感了 皮尔森是个该死的腋窝
You know, you're too sentimental, Bill. Pilsen's a goddamn armpit.
只适合嫖娼
Only good for whoring.
他们的领导是在皮尔森
Their leadership is in Pilsen.
-你知道吗 -我正在努力
-You know that for a fact? -I'm working on it.
速度不够快
Not fast enough.
如果我们做我们的工作 我们可以找到线程的末端 它们的第一个
If we do our job, we can locate the end of the thread, their Number One,
解开整个网络
and unravel the whole network.
听着 让我在那儿拦住你
Look, let me stop you right there.
嘿 那艘船已经开航了
Hey, that ship has sailed.
我必须向他们解释为什么在那里
And I have to explain why to them in there.
我在士兵场找到了一个身份证 那是我追踪了两年的人
I got a positive ID at Soldier Field, the man I've been tracking for two years.
我需要时间让他活着进来
I need time to bring him in alive.
你没在听
You're not listening.
现在 我们有了资源
Right now, we have resources behind us.
现在 你可能看不到他们 但他们在那里 他们在保护你
Now, you might not see them, but they're there. They're protecting you.
你变得越不理智 发出的噪音就越不必要
And the more irrational you become, the more unnecessary noise you make,
邀请你上救生艇就越难了
the harder it's gonna be to invite you into the lifeboat.
你明白我的意思吗
Do you understand me?
如果有机会从这片垂死的岩石上下来
If there's any chance of getting off this dying rock,
我不会浪费它的
I'm not gonna waste it.
皮尔森已经死了
Pilsen is already dead.
他们只是还不知道
They just don't know it yet.
他们讨厌我们的气味
They hate the way we smell.
那怎么样
How about that?
对不起 我得把你留在这里 比尔 不能带任何人和我在一起
Sorry I got to leave you here, Bill. Can't take anybody with me.
如果你只知道这里面是什么
If you only knew what was inside this place.
局长的特权 先生
The commissioner's privilege, sir.
你知道的
You know it.
别挂断电话 比尔 玩球
And don't get hung up on this, Bill. Play ball.
保持双手清洁 让猎人干脏活
And keep your hands clean. Let the hunters do the dirty work.
我会告诉下面的朋友 他们得到了我们的全面运营支持
And I'll tell our friends down below they got our full operational support.
现在 回家 放松 休息一次 嗯
Now, go home, relax, take the night off for once, huh?
所有的二级坦克现在都加压了
All the second-stage tanks now pressurized.
35秒后开始计数
Thirty-five seconds and counting.
我们还在走 三十秒后开始计数
We are still go. Thirty seconds and counting.
感觉很好 现在减去25
Feels good. T-minus 25 now.
比尔 让我们骑这个出去
Let's ride this one out, Bill.
确认等级和身份
Confirming rank and identity.
尤金・伊戈委员
Commissioner Eugene Igoe.
让他们带头 直到它消失
Let them take the lead. Just until it dies down.
安全许可完成
Security clearance complete.
-十 九…-准备降落
-Ten, nine... -Prepare for descent.
点火顺序启动
Ignition sequence start.
六 五 四 三 二 一
Six, five, four, three, two, one.
我现在不能保护你
I can't protect you now.
我知道
I know.
我对你有信心
I have faith in you.
为什么
Why?
你为什么 其他人都没有
Why do you? Nobody else does.
我们可以一起走
We could go away together.
这不是我们的故事
That's not our story.
和我一起跳舞
Dance with me.
你有工作要做
You have a job to do.
快 快 快 走吧 走吧
Move, move, move! Let's go! Let's go!
回来 往后退
Get back! Move back!
爸爸 醒醒
Dad, Wake up!
你得走了 你得后退 快点
You got to get moving now! You got to move back! Hurry up!
妈妈 醒醒 妈妈 醒醒 特色菜来了
Mom, wake up. Mom, wake up. Specials are here!
所有人 马上趴在地上 趴下 趴下
Everyone, get on the ground now! Get down! Get down!
有好东西  醒醒
Specials are here! Specials are here! Specials are here! Wake up!
就是这样 够了
That's it. Enough of this shit!
快 快 快
Move, move, move!
别转头 面对墙
Don't turn your head. Face the wall!
特价商品 特色菜来了
Specials! Specials are here!
现在就行动
Move now!
-加布里埃尔・德拉蒙德 -把手放在墙上
-Gabriel Drummond. -Get your hands on the wall.
你认识他吗 你见过他吗
Do you know him? Have you seen him?
拉斐尔・德拉蒙德 谁认识他
Rafael Drummond. Who knows him?
-把手放在墙上 -嘿 看这里有什么
-Hands on the wall. -Hey, look what we got here.
嘿 你从哪儿弄到这么多钱的
Hey, where'd you get all this money, huh?
你卖什么来得到这些钱？ 携带武器
What are you selling to get all that money? Carry a weapon?
我问你一个问题 朋克
I asked you a question, punk.
和我一起试试那个牛仔的狗屎 让我们看看去哪儿 嗯
Try that cowboy shit with me? Let's see where that goes, huh?
你在开玩笑吧
Are you kidding me?
现在谁是牛仔
Who the cowboy now, huh?
嗯
Huh?
你要怎么做 加布里埃尔
What are you gonna do, Gabriel?
开枪打死他
Shoot him?
去吧 开枪
Go ahead, shoot.
杀了那个混蛋 你知道这会让你感觉更好
Kill the bastard. You know it'll make you feel better.
快点 别再生气了
Come on, get rid of some of that rage.
-把他们都带进去 -快 快 快
-Take them all in. -Move, move, move!
在这附近 我们射杀自己的人
In this neighborhood, we shoot our own guys.
针对一名男子 拉斐尔・德鲁蒙德 进行了假体植入
Target one man, Rafael Drummond, moving on a fraudulent implant.
你好
Hello?
很抱歉我以前不能说
I'm sorry I couldn't say it before.
我是为查理做的
I'm doing this for Charlie.
这里有人想和你谈谈
There's someone here who wants to talk to you.
你好 埃文 告诉我们你的朋友要去哪里
Hello, Evan. Tell us where your friends are going.
这是一条安全信息 如果你看到什么 说点什么
This is a security message. If you see something, say something.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
最后一个去纽约和蒙特利尔的巴士上车的电话
last call for boarding for buses heading to New York City and Montreal,
出发时间为7:00
departure set for 7:00.
所有单位 站住 必要的狩猎单位旅行
All units, stand down. Requisite hunter units traveling.
我不想进去
I don't want to go in.
最后一次登机
Last call for boarding
去纽约和蒙特利尔的巴士
for buses heading to New York City and Montreal.
只要把门推开就行了
Just push the door and come through.
我不想进去
I don't want to go in.
你让我们迟到了 查理 你能把门推一下吗
You're making us late, Charlie. Would you just push the door.
好的
Fine.
谢谢您 非常感谢
Thank you. Thank you very much.
现在就趴在地上
On the ground now!
双手放在脑后
Hands behind your head!
坐下来 坐下来
Sit down! Sit down!
嘿
Hey!
你 马上下来 我说了下去
You! Get down now! I said down!
还没有结束
It's not over.
有人杀了我
Somebody kill me!
我想要个律师
I want a lawyer.
再过十年…
In another ten...
九个半小时后 皮尔森就什么都没有了
nine and a half hours, there'll be nothing left of Pilsen.
我说我想要个律师
I said I want a lawyer.
你和我都知道那些日子已经过去了
You and I both know those days are gone.
我烧了你的船不需要搜查令
I didn't need a warrant when I burned your boat.
你现在为我工作 加布里埃尔
You work for me now, Gabriel.
我告诉过你…
I told you...
我不是你的毒品
I'm not one of your narcs.
我不会为你做狗屎的
I'm not gonna do shit for you.
我不是要你为我做任何事
I'm not asking you to do anything for me.
我甚至没有要求你为你的社区做任何事
I'm not even asking you to do anything for your community.
即使很多人都会死去
Even though plenty of people are going to die.
像你父亲一样 你更像一个家庭成员
Like your father, you're more of a family guy.
先血
Blood first.
你最后一次见到你弟弟是什么时候
When's the last time you saw your brother?
我不会告诉你的
I'm not gonna tell you shit.
所以你想对我做什么就做什么
So you can do whatever you want to do to me.
你有个访客
You got a visitor.
家庭日
Family day.
你想说点什么
You want to say something?
前进 他能听见你说话
Go ahead. He can hear you.
弟弟 为什么…
Baby brother, why...
你为什么不听
Why didn't you listen?
你在这里干什么 伙计
What you doing here, man?
不
No.
不 不 加布 嘿 别这样
No! No! Gabe! Hey, don't!
别让他们利用你 你听见了吗 你听见了吗
Don't let 'em use you! You hear me? You hear me?
伙计 我告诉过你不要…我告诉过你不要做英雄 雷夫
Man, I told you not... I told you not to be a hero, Rafe.
-别这么做 -我告诉过你不要做英雄
-Don't do it! -I told you not to be the hero!
听着 别这样 加布
Look, don't do it, Gabe.
我告诉过你 我已经死了 伙计
I told you, I'm already dead, man.
去做吧 我会确保他活着的
Do it, and I'll make sure he lives.
你希望我相信你
You expect me to trust you?
加布 你在吗 加布
Gabe, you there? Gabe?
艹
Fuck!
仔细听我说 加布里埃尔
Listen to me carefully, Gabriel.
现在 立法者正准备将皮尔森调平
Right now, the Legislators are preparing to level Pilsen
因为你哥哥的所作所为
for what your brother's done.
他们用同样的方法平整了柳条公园
Same way they leveled Wicker Park.
我们的总结结束了
Our roundups are over.
你是我们进入网络的唯一途径
You are our one way into the network.
我需要你从凤凰城传递信息
I need you to deliver a message from the Phoenix.
你不会问问题的
You will not ask questions.
照我说的做 你哥哥就活了
Do exactly what I say, and your brother will live.
明白了吗
Understand?
当你以前想送东西的时候 你去哪里了
When you wanted to deliver something before, where did you go?
把它们给他们
Give them this.
那是加布吗
Is that Gabe?
你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
我收到凤凰社的消息
I got a message from the Phoenix.
他在车里
He's inside the van.
快点 伙计 快点 快点
Come on, man, move, move!
门开了
The door's open.
给他看你给我看的
Show him what you showed me.
不要 不要 不要 不要
Don't, don't, don't. Don't.
我是雷夫的哥哥
I'm Rafe's brother.
把它放下
Put it down.
这里没有雷夫
There's no Rafe here.
你想要什么
What do you want?
你怎么知道的
How'd you know about this?
打电话
Make the call.
物体向西移动
Subject moving west.
-现在 老板 -还没有
-Now, boss? -Not yet.
你应该已经走了
You should've left already.
不 我们的命令要一直到最后
No, our orders are to stay until the end.
我想这就是结局
I think this is the end.
他们在公共汽车站抓住了他
They got him at the bus station.
如果我们弄错了怎么办
What if we got it wrong?
他要求被带到第一位
He's asking to be taken to Number One.
他说他知道进入封闭区的方法
Says he knows a way into the Closed Zone.
加布里埃尔
Gabriel?
你认识他吗
You know him?
他是我的学生
He was a student of mine.
那么 我们现在该怎么办
So, what do we do now?
把信息传递给第一位
Deliver the message to Number One.
主题向北移动
Subject moving north.
主题旅行
Subject traveling.
所有单位 保持在视线之外
All units, remain out of sight.
是皮尔森妓院
It's the Pilsen brothel.
跟着她上楼
Follow her upstairs.
现在我们走
Now we go.
-好吧 -快 快 快
-All right! -Move, move, move!
你好 加布里埃尔
Hello, Gabriel.
怎样
How...
你怎么知道我的名字
how do you know my name?
现在
Now.
-下来 加油 别动 枪
-Down! Come on! Don't move! -Gun!
站下来 直到我到达
Stand down until I arrive.
你知道这个地方吗
You know this place?
不
No.
胡克是个历史迷
Hooker is a history buff.
剪辑是空的 我不明白
Clip's empty. I don't get it.
呵呵
Huh.
只有墙上的照片
Only picture on the wall.
这是我们吗
This us?
这是她自己的安排
It's her own setup.
到封闭区域的通信线路现在打开
Communication line to the Closed Zone is now open.
姓名 级别 部门
Name, rank, department.
威廉・穆里根
Mulligan, William.
指挥官 皮尔森特别分行
Commander. Pilsen Special Branch.
让我们开始汇报吧 继续进行
Let's begin the debrief. Proceed.
我们找到的计算机包含所有名称 别名和位置
The computer we found contained all names, aliases and locations
芝加哥网络
of the Chicago network.
这封信比限制条件早了几年
This communication sent some years before restrictions.
国家网络的证明
Proof of a national network.
电脑中那个是妓女吗
The computer belonged to the prostitute?
第一
Number One.
她录下了她和约翰的互动
She recorded her interactions with her johns
并通过网络链发送相关信息
and sent relevant information out through the network's chain.
她的副手是通讯部的查尔斯・里滕豪斯
Her second in command was Charles Rittenhouse, communications,
负责激活被称为凤凰城的行动
responsible for activating the operation known as Phoenix.
去吧 当选
Go. Get in.
第三 帕特里克埃利森 运营部
Number three, Patrick Ellison, operations.
-退场前…-在这里等着
-Before demobilization... -Wait here.
…海军陆战队 军械
...Marine Corps, ordnance.
等等 等等 不 我和你住在一起 我要和你在一起
Wait, wait. No. I'm staying with you. I'm staying with you!
第四 劳尔・卡西利亚斯 材料和运输
Number four, Raul Casillas, materials and transport.
皮尔森汽车厂的工头
Foreman at the Pilsen Auto Yards.
系统分析师伊凡列维耶夫
Systems analyst Ivan Leviev
侵入我们的中央监控数据库
hacked into our central surveillance database
并追踪了副市长罗伯特・沃茨 他是炸弹的情报员
and tracked Deputy Mayor Robert Watts, the unwitting courier of the bomb.
关闭前的医科学生 哈里森马
Harrison Ma, a medical student before the closures,
开发了移除身份植入物的程序
developed a procedure to remove identity implants,
使手机对无人机保持隐形
enabling the cell to remain invisible to tracker drones.
这些是隐藏在眼前的主要人物
These were the principals hiding in plain sight
是谁让这个小分队在战场上发动攻击的
who enabled the cell to carry out the attack on Soldier Field.
对武装分子嫌疑犯的搜查已经加速
The search for militant suspects has accelerated.
据报道 一名身份不明的女性居民被枪杀
An unidentified female resident is reported to have been shot and killed.
但一旦我们有了他们的头号
But once we had their Number One,
他们知道我们也有
they knew we had them, too.
芝加哥网络…
The Chicago network...
被中和
is neutralized.
她的名字和背景是什么
What was her name and background?
她的名字叫普里西拉・斯科特
Her name was Priscilla Scott.
她是皮尔森小学的历史老师
She was a history teacher at Pilsen Elementary.
她已经九年没有上网了 所以我们对她一无所知
She was off the grid for nine years, so there's nothing else we know about her.
妓女为什么
A prostitute. Why?
访问
Access.
她非常仔细地为客户服务 为团结政府的成员提供服务
She groomed her clients very carefully, procured members of the Unity government,
操纵他们泄露机密信息
and manipulated them into divulging classified information,
她用隐藏的电线记录下来的
which she recorded with her concealed wire.
请放录音带
Play the tape, please.
你能想象他们在下面做什么吗
Can you imagine what they do down there?
剥去一切
Stripping everything.
每个裂缝 经常水力压裂
Every crevasse. Fracking to the power often.
把一切都从地球上带走
Taking it all off planet.
你感觉到了地震
You felt those earthquakes.
他们会匍匐前进 他们站着
They'll crawl. They stand.
对他们来说都一样
It's all the same to them.
他们有地下隧道网…
They have this network of tunnels under the surface...
等待 你在禁区内
Wait. You've been inside the Closed Zone?
不 不是我 专员
No, not me. The commissioner.
他就是那个有权进入的人
He's the guy with the access.
好吧 那我们最好把生意让开
Well, then we better get business out of the way.
是的 这是一件大事
Yeah, it's a big deal.
他们多久从封闭区出来一次
How often do they come out of the Closed Zone?
罗伯特・沃茨 他就是这位议员的推销员
Robert Watts, he's just this alderman's bagman,
但他会在集会上处理他们
but he'll be handling them out at the rally.
问候他们 带他们进来
Greeting them, taking them in.
这是一项不可思议的责任
That's an incredible responsibility.
嗯 如果我告诉你蟑螂总督可能是他们中的一员呢
Mm-hmm. What if I told you that the roach governor may be one of them?
-哦…-请停止录音
-Oh... -Stop the tape, please.
尤金
Eugene.
我们自己的指挥链被破坏了
Our own chain of command was compromised.
那你呢
What about you?
我呢
What about me?
你住在这附近
You live in this neighborhood.
对
Yes.
这些是你的人
These are your people.
立法机构将分析证据
Evidence will be analyzed by the Legislature.
同时 作为代理专员
In the meantime, as acting commissioner,
你要向封闭区报到以获得进一步的订单
you are to report to the Closed Zone for further orders.
别再问了
No more questions.
装货
Loading up!
单个文件中的行
Lines in a single file.
雷夫还活着
Rafe's alive.
是啊 那又怎么样
Yeah, so what?
我对他不再意味着什么了
I don't mean nothing to him anymore.
-你有一个目标 -没有目的
-You had a purpose. -There was no purpose.
雷夫的计划失败了
Rafe's plan failed.
如果计划失败怎么办
What if the plan was to fail?
就像我说的 你现在为我工作
Like I said, you work for me now.
你想让我怎么办
And what do you want me to do with this?
加布里埃尔 你在历史课上注意过吗
Did you pay attention in history class, Gabriel?
提防带礼物的希腊人
Beware of Greeks bearing gifts.
现在 滚出去
Now, get out.
穆里根委员 他们让你成为大人物 比尔
Commissioner Mulligan. They made you the big man, Bill.
你下来的时候要当心我们 局长
Look out for us when you get down there, Commissioner.
我们到了
Here we are.
哦 上帝 约翰尼 不 嗯 我都出汗了
Oh, Lord. Johnny, no. Well, I'm all sweaty.
-来吧 宝贝 你看起来很漂亮 -不…
-Come on, baby, you look beautiful. -No...
-普里斯 查尔斯 -嗨
-Priss, Charles! -Hi!
历史老师的忠告
Words of advice from a history teacher
给下一代
to the future generation?
嗨 宝贝加布里埃尔 我等不及要拥抱你了
Hi, baby Gabriel. I can't wait to cuddle you.
这不是建议
That's not advice.
比尔 你呢
Bill, how about you?
约翰 我下班了 你有问题 打911
I'm off duty, John. You got a problem, call 911.
站起来 你知道Priss
Get up here. You know Priss.
她和我妻子在学校教书
She teaches at the school with my wife.
-嗨 你好吗 -普里斯
-Hi. How are you? -Priss.
比尔 有什么建议吗
Bill, any advice?
哦 是的
Oh, yeah.
老师还是警察 孩子 你必须做出选择
Teacher or cop, kid? You got to make a choice.
无论你是谁 都要做一个好人
Whatever you are, be a good one.
孩子 你家真是太好了
You got a hell of a family here, kid.
谢谢 -不仅仅是他们 我们所有人
-Thank you. -And not just them. All of us.
皮尔森掩护了你
Pilsen's got you covered.
未来是你的 孩子
The future is yours, kid.
确认等级和身份
Confirming rank and identity.
威廉・穆里根委员
Commissioner William Mulligan.
安全许可完成
Security clearance complete.
准备降落
Prepare for descent.
15秒 指导是内部的
Fifteen seconds. Guidance is internal.
12 11 10 9…
12, 11, ten, nine...
点火顺序启动
Ignition sequence start.
六 五 四 三 二 一
Six, five, four, three, two, one.
掉下来
Drop.
点燃火柴
Light a match.
点燃一场战争
Ignite a war.
只要我们反击 我们就有机会
Long as we fight back, we got a chance.